https://alpensierracoffee.com/privacy-policy/

PRIVACY POLICY
IntroductionThis is the official Privacy Policy of Alpen Sierra Coffee Roasting Company (“ASC,” “we,” “us,” or “our”), is a coffee roasting business. The official website for ASC is www.alpensierracoffee.com (“Site”). Where you are new to ASC to repeat customer of ASC we are committed to protecting the privacy of our customers who visit our Site.This Privacy Policy explains:• The type of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) we collect,• What we use it for,• With who we will share it with,• How we will protect it and• How to contact us with any concerns.This Site is governed by laws and regulations of the United States (“U.S.”). If you are not a resident of the U.S. you hereby freely consent to the transfer and processing of your Personal Information to the U.S. and you consent to be governed by the laws and regulations of the U.S. with regards to the use of your Personal Information.
2. Personal InformationPersonal Information includes your name, address, phone number and e-mail address and any other information that is associated with your Personal Information. In the U.S., “Sensitive Personal Information” is personally identifiable information that is more confidential or sensitive in nature, such as your credit or debit card account number, social security number, and driver’s license. This Privacy Policy governs all forms of Personal Information collected and used by the ASC offline and online.
3. ModificationWe reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time without prior notice. When we modify the Policy, we will post the revised Policy on this Site.
4. Collection and Use of Personal InformationThe Site allows you to input information to help make your business transaction with us an excellent experience. The information ASC collects includes your name, address, email address, password, telephone number, order information, additional contact information, IP address, cookies, credit card number, banking information and any other additional information you may wish to share with us.There are 2 ways we collect your personal information:Information you give us. We collect Personal Information online and offline only if you choose to provide it to us. IP addresses and cookies information may be collected pursuant to paragraph below 8. ASC does not collect home addresses, home phone numbers, e-mail addresses, payment information, and order information unless you decide to provide this information to the ASC. If you choose to send us personal information, we are not responsible for any data breach as a result of the method of your data transfer.Information we get from use of our services. We may collect information about the services that you use and how you use them, like when you visit a website that uses our advertising services or you view and interact with our ads and content.This information includes:Device information: We may collect device-specific information (such as your hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information including phone number). ASC may associate your device identifiers or phone number with your ASC Account.Log information: When you use our services or view content provided by ASC, we may automatically collect and store certain information in server logs.This may include:Details of how you used our service, such as your search queries.Telephony log information like your phone number, calling-party number, forwarding numbers, time and date of calls, duration of calls, SMS routing information and types of calls.Internet protocol address.Device event information such as crashes, system activity, hardware settings, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and referral URL.Cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your ASC Account.Location information When you use a location-enabled ASC service, we may collect and process information about your actual location, like GPS signals sent by a mobile device. We may also use various technologies to determine location, such as sensor data from your device that may, for example, provide information on nearby Wi-Fi access points and cell towers.Unique application numbers Certain services include a unique application number. This number and information about your installation (for example, the operating system type and application version number) may be sent to ASC when you install or uninstall that service or when that service periodically contacts our servers, such as for automatic updates.Local storage We may collect and store information (including personal information) locally on your device using mechanisms such as browser web storage (including HTML 5) and application data caches.Cookies and anonymous identifiers We use various technologies to collect and store information when you visit our Site and this may include sending one or more cookies or anonymous identifiers to your device. We also use cookies and anonymous identifiers when you interact with services we offer to our partners, such as advertising services or ASC features that may appear on other sites. More information can be found in paragraph 8.
5. How Personal Information Is SharedFor payments made offline, we submit the Personal Information needed to secure payment to the appropriate clearinghouse. If payment is submitted online, we use an authorized third-party operational service provider to collect and process your Personal Information in a reasonably secure manner. Our operational service provider may also collect the security code associated with the credit or debit card. Please review the privacy policy of our operational service provider which is separate and may be different from ASC’s privacy policy.Credit card information may be stored for future purchases. Your Personal Information may be shared with any current or future subsidiaries or partners. We never sell, share, or otherwise give out any mail or email addresses to other vendors.When individuals choose to pay by check, we do not store checking account information. Payment information is retained for administrative and tax purposes.To the extent permitted by law, we may disclose your Personal Information to government authorities or third parties pursuant to a legal request, subpoena, or to comply with other legal process. We may also use or disclose your Personal Information to protect the rights or property of the ASC, and the rights, safety or security of our employees, our Site or its users, and to enforce our Terms of Use Agreement.
6. The Children’s Online Privacy Protection RuleASC does not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. Any Personal Information knowingly collected from a child via the Site will be deleted. Should you have knowledge that a child under the age of 13 has submitted their Personal Information on ASC’s website please contact ASC at coffeentea@alpensierra.com.
7. Cookies and Other TechnologyBy using our Site, some information may be automatically collected by our web servers as you browse our Site. For example, our web server automatically collects information known as “click stream data,” such as the domain name of the site providing you with Internet access, the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your browser type and version, operating system and platform, the average time spent on our site, pages viewed, information searched for, access times and other relevant statistics. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information in the interest of improving our site and service.“Cookies” provide visitors a personalized experience on our site by enabling us to determine unique preferences and trends based on visits to our website and to other websites. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies; however, you can usually change your browser to prevent or notify you whenever you are sent a cookie. This gives you the chance to decide whether or not to accept the cookie. A “cookie” does not tell us who you are, your email address, or any other personal information. We use the information it provides to help us improve the site and our service, and to provide our visitors with a better experience, while on the site. Even without accepting a cookie you can still access most of the features on the site. There will, however, be limitations on your use of some site functions. For example, if you choose to disable cookies you will not be able to view your orders on-line, store or update your user profile, or take advantage of promotional discounts.Some of links to other websites may use cookies. Since these partners set and read cookies using their own servers, we have no access to, or control over them. However, cookies do not permit access to confidential personal information about site visitors; rather they are used to keep track of traffic to the site.
8. Protecting Your Personal Information
ASC is committed to protecting the security of your Personal Information. We use reasonable security technologies and procedures to protect your Personal Information and use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), the industry standard for secure commerce transactions to transmit your credit card information over the Internet. This means your credit card number is scrambled during the transaction process, so that the information cannot be read as it travels over the Internet.
We restrict access to personal information to ASC employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for us.
9. Process To Access and Review of Personal InformationIf you would like to review, modify and/or correct your own Personal Information, please contact us at coffeentea@alpensierra.com. You must authenticate your identity before we provide access to your Personal Information.We may reject requests that are unreasonably repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort (for example, developing a new system or fundamentally changing an existing practice), risk the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes).Where we can provide information access and correction, we will do so for free, except where it would require a disproportionate effort. We aim to maintain our services in a manner that protects information from accidental or malicious destruction. Because of this, after you delete information from our services, we may not immediately delete residual copies from our active servers and may not remove information from our backup systems.
10. External LinksIn order to assist you and provide you with as much information as possible, our Site contains links to other websites including those that offer information of interest. The privacy policy of ASC does not apply to the websites which ASC links to. Please review the separate privacy policy of any linked websites.
11. Contact UsIf you have any questions or comments, please contact us at:WebMaster Alpen Sierra Coffee Roasting Company2222 Park Place, 1A  Minden, NV 89423coffeentea@alpensierracoffee.com1-800-531-1405
